{
  "chapter": 5,
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "Which cloud service is considered as the most widely used?",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Infrastructure-as-a-Service",
        "Platform-as-a-Service",
        "Software-as-a-Service",
        "All of these"
      ],
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Which cloud service is known as Hardware-as-a-Service also?",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Infrastructure-as-a-Service",
        "Platform-as-a-Service",
        "Software-as-a-Service",
        "Desktop-as-a-Service"
      ],
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Which among the following describes a distribution model in which applications are hosted by a service provider and made available to users?",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Infrastructure-as-a-Service",
        "Platform-as-a-Service",
        "Software-as-a-Service",
        "All of these"
      ],
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Virtual machine in Rackspace cloud is called",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Rackspace Server",
        "Cloud Server",
        "RackVM",
        "None of these"
      ],
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Identify the odd one",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Microsoft Azure",
        "Google App Engine",
        "Force.com",
        "Amazon EC2"
      ],
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "In IaaS, computing resources are delivered to the consumers",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Through remote access",
        "Through distribution",
        "In virtualized form",
        "None of these"
      ],
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Which is not considered as one of the three main categories of cloud services?",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Software-as-a-Service",
        "Database-as-a-Service",
        "Platform-as-a-Service",
        "Infrastructure-as-a-Service"
      ],
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Which cloud computing service model delivers computer, storage, and network to consumers?",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Infrastructure-as-a-Service",
        "Platform-as-a-Service",
        "Software-as-a-Service",
        "All of these"
      ],
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Retaining with traditional computing environment costs more compared to using cloud computing.",
      "incorrect_answers": ["True", "False"],
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Name of the Open-source cloud computing PaaS facility originally developed by VMWare as",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "VMWare platform",
        "Cloud foundry",
        "VMW-PaaS",
        "None of these"
      ],
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Eucalyptus, Nebula, Nimbus, CloudStack, VLC are few examples of",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Open-source cloud services",
        "Closed source cloud services",
        "Proprietary cloud services",
        "Free cloud services"
      ],
      "answer": 1
    }
  ]
}
